A Guide to the Records of the Communications Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1994 (bulk 1990-1993).
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. News Summaries, 1990 June-1994 Jan (Acc. 35539)., Extent: 22 cubic feet (22 boxes). (Box 3-24)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 9. (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 10. (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 11. (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 12. (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 15. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 16. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 17. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 18. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 19. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 22. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 23. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 24. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 25. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 26. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 29. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 30. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Mar 31. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 1. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 2. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 5. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 6. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 7. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 8. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 9. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 12. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 13. (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 14. (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 15. (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 16. (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 19. (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 20. (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 21. (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 22. (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 23. (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 26. (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 27. (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 28. (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 29. (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Apr 30. (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 3. (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 4. (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 5. (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 6. (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 7. (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 10. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 11. (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 12. (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 13. (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 14. (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 17. (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 18. (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 19. (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 20. (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 21. (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 24. (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 25. (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 26. (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 27. (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - News Summaries, 1993 May 28. (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 1. (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 2. (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 3. (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 4. (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 7. (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 8. (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 9. (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 10. (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 11. (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 14. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 15. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 16. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 17. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 18. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 21. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 22. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 23. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 24. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 25. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 28. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 29. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1993 June 30. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 1. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 2. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 6. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 7. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 8. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 9. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 12. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 13. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 14. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 15. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 16. (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 19. (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 20. (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 21. (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 22. (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 23. (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 26. (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 27. (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 28. (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 29. (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1993 July 30. (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 2. (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 3. (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 4. (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 5. (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 6. (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 9. (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 10. (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 11. (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 12. (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 13. (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 16. (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 17. (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 18. (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 19. (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 20. (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 23. (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 24. (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 25. (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 26. (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 27. (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 30. (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Aug 31. (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 1. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 2. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 3. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 7. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 8. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 9. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 10. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 13. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 14. (Box 23, Folder 8a)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 15-16. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 17. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 20. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 21. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 22. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 23. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 24. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 27. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 28. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 29. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Sept 30. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 1. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 4. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 5. (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 6. (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 7. (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 8. (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 14-15. (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 18. (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 19. (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 20. (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 21. (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 22. (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 25. (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 26. (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 27. (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 28. (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Oct 29. (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 1. (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 2. (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 3. (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 4. (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 5. (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 8. (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 9. (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 10. (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 12. (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 15. (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 16. (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 17. (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 18. (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 19. (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 22. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 23. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 24. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 29. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Nov 30. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 1. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 2. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 3. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 6. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 7. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 8. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 9. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 10. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 13. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 15. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 16. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 17. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 20. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 21. (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 22. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1993 Dec 29. (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1994 Jan 3. (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1994 Jan 7. (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1994 Jan 11. (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1994 Jan 13. (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1994 Jan 14. (Box 24, Folder 27)